{
    "subject": "resource/Thomas_Lough",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Thomas_Lough",
    "human_readable": "Thomas Lough is primarily about Thomas Lough.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9784767031669617,
            "question": "What is Thomas Lough primarily about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8816435933113098,
            "question": "Who is Thomas Lough?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8237087726593018,
            "question": "What are some key facts about Thomas Lough?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.797284722328186,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Thomas Lough?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7455205917358398,
            "question": "Are there any notable works or achievements associated with Thomas Lough?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7273253798484802,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Thomas Lough's family or background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7134013772010803,
            "question": "Where is Thomas Lough from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7033419609069824,
            "question": "Is there any specific field or area that Thomas Lough is known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6902253031730652,
            "question": "What are some interesting things to know about Thomas Lough's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.53346848487854,
            "question": "When was Thomas Lough born?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Thomas Lough is primarily about Thomas Lough.",
            "html": "dbpedia_982_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some interesting things to know about Thomas Lough's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_982_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any specific field or area that Thomas Lough is known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_982_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Thomas Lough from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_982_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_982_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_982_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_982_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_982_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_982_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_982_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_982_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_982_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_982_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_982_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Thomas Lough, discussing his life and career as an artist, poet, and musician. Therefore, the statement that the documents are primarily about Thomas Lough is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information provided contains multiple facts about different Thomas Loughs, making it impossible for the statement \"Thomas Lough is primarily about Thomas Lough\" to be accurate.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}